<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Abouts on Jabbar&#39;s General Contracting</title>
    <link>https://jabbars-general-contracting.github.io/about/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Abouts on Jabbar&#39;s General Contracting</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://jabbars-general-contracting.github.io/about/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://jabbars-general-contracting.github.io/about/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jabbars-general-contracting.github.io/about/about/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Jabbar&amp;rsquo;s General Contracting was developed in 1983 under the name Jabbar&amp;rsquo;s Carpenter Service
in Houston Texas, a sole proprietorship which became a partnership and returned to a sole proprietorship in 1991.
The owner, Rahim Jabbar, was trained since high school in building and construction. Trained also in architectural
drafting Mr. Jabbar was able to establish a building and construction business that combined technical drawing freestyle art
with building experience to create a company distinctly capable of producing a unique design and vision in
construction and renovation that separates the company from any other.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Over the past 35 years this establishment has been responsible for building some of the most glamorous
private homes in the country, and renovations that prove the concepts of building
and construction are limitless. &lt;a href=&#34;tel:14092398995&#34;&gt;Call Mr. Jabbar&lt;/a&gt; with your building and renovation concerns
and allow him to take you through journey that will enlighten your building ideas and stimulate your taste for superb living.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>